infinitemonkeys.mobi 2016-05-14

# App Creator Software Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to www.infinitemonkeys.mobi owned and operated by Infinite Monkeys (“We”, “Us”, “Our”). This privacy policy describes how Infinite Monkeys collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: [//www.infinitemonkeys.mobi.](https://www.infinitemonkeys.mobi./) It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Infinite Monkeys has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this English language Web site, [//www.infinitemonkeys.mobi](https://www.infinitemonkeys.mobi/) and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile applications, mobile devices that use our apps, affiliated brand websites or social networking plug-ins.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@infinitemonkeys.com.](mailto:privacy@infinitemonkeys.com.)  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here.](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or create a "Profile". When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information (and billing info). You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
    •    To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
    •    To process transactions   
    •    To fulfill your order  
    •    To send you an order confirmation  
    •    To respond to customer service requests  
    •    To administer your account  
    •    To improve our Web site and marketing efforts  
    •    To conduct research and analysis  
    •    To send periodic emails (The email address you provide may be used to send you information, send you a newsletter or other promotional messages, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.)

**How do we protect your information?**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [privacy@infinitemonkeys.com](mailto:privacy@infinitemonkeys.com)

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it) that enables the sites or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use these cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, for example. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can disable and/or remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited.

    •    Web Beacons

We and third party advertising partners employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

    •    Analytics

As is true of most web sites, we also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

    •    Online Advertising / Behavioral Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/) . Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. This includes the use of trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing customer service, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also release your information when required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others or investigate fraud. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

If Infinite Monkeys is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

**How can you access your information?**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by making the change in your account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at [privacy@infinitemonkeys.com](mailto:privacy@infinitemonkeys.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter or blog posts, we will use your name and email address to send the emails to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving these emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [privacy@infinitemonkeys.com.](mailto:privacy@infinitemonkeys.com.)

**Third Party links**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Infinite Monkeys. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and if you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Twitter button, Share This button or other interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Our Blog**

Our Web site offers a publically accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide in this area may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. You can request the removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, by contacting us at [privacy@infinitemonkeys.com.](mailto:privacy@infinitemonkeys.com.) In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Single Sign-On**

You can register and log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect, Twitter, Yahoo, Google & OpenID. These services will authenticate your identity and send us a non-identifiable validation code.. Services like Facebook Connect may give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us:**

Infinite Monkeys  
299 Pavonia Ave #3-1  
Jersey City, New Jersey  
USA, 07302  
privacy@infinitemonkeys.com

This policy was last modified on March 4, 2014
